<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jacob Milligan</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jacob Milligan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 03:31:54 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Site!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 03:31:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/new-site/</guid>
      <description>I decided to move my site over from tumblr to something a little nicer to work with. Tumblr is definitely one of the major reasons I post pretty infrequently as I really don&amp;rsquo;t like working with it at all.
So I&amp;rsquo;ve got a slick new site using Hugo and let me tell you something - it&amp;rsquo;s a lot nicer to work with. I tried a few static site generators, primarily Jekyll and Gatsby, and just really enjoyed working with Huge mainly because it&amp;rsquo;s insanely fast - seriously you never realize how slow your static site generator is until you use Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diamond-Square In C#</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/diamond-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 00:08:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/diamond-square/</guid>
      <description>Fractals are cool! They’re indispensable for procedural generation - things like clouds, heightmaps, moisture maps etc.
They can make things like this:
With an accompanying heightmap (This is actually Simplex Noise from my current project):
Unfortunately they can be pretty difficult to wrap your head around when getting started, there are a bunch of often-mentioned algorithms and techniques used to generate this stuff - Perlin Noise, Simplex Noise, Value Noise being a few, and they all have their pros and cons (value noise looks real bad though, so it’s mostly cons and latticing).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>